

#### CONTACTS



Majalengka, October 9th, 1999



**ADDRESS** 

Majalengka, Jawa Barat



#### PHONE

+62857 1062 5293



EMAIL

teguhammart@gmail.com

#### SOCIAL MEDIA



## LINKEDIN

bit.ly/LinkedinTeguh

#### ACHIEVEMENT

Mar, 2021 Winner 1st

**Statistics Infographic Competition** Gadjah Mada University

Oct, 2020 Expectation Winner 2<sup>nd</sup> **National Statistics Challenge** Brawijaya University

#### CERTIFICATION AND SKILL

Familiar with Microsoft (Word, Excel, Power Point), R, Python, QGIS, SPSS, and Tableau.

Strong in Discipline, Teamwork, Hardwork, Dare to Try, and Spirit.

#### GRANTEE

Paragon Scholarship Program 2021

#### LANGUAGE

Indonesian

English

# **TEGUH AMMAR**



## DATA ANALYST

#### PROFILE

Hello! I am Teguh Ammar Taqiyyuddin, one of the students at Padjadjaran University. I have experience in statistics and have an interest in Data Analysts. Discipline, responsibility, smart work, and high enthusiasm can make a positive contribution to the company.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2018 - Now O Bachelor's degree

Statistics, Padjadjaran University

GPA: 3.95 of 4.00

2015-2018 O Senior High School of

SMAN 1 Majalengka National Exam: 315 of 400

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Assistant Lecturer | Feb 2020 - Now

Statistics, Padjadjaran University

Provide software training, prepare teaching materials, assist lecturers in student assessment.

Feb 2021 - Now

OTime Series Data Analysis

Aug 2020 - Jan 2021 O Experimental Design and Analysis

Feb 2020 - Jul 2020 O Exploration Data Analysis

#### Statistical Consultant | Mar 2020 - Now

Jatinangor Research Center

Provide analysis to clients in the form of data input, data processing, and explanation of data analysis.

### Research and Development Specialist | Mar 2020 -

Social Media of Infojatinangor

Provide data analysis for social media development projects in the form of Instagram insights.

## **Surveyor** | Nov 2019 PT. Dyandra Promosindo

Conducted a survey on visitor and participants satisfaction of Kicfest 2019,

#### INTRERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

#### Sectoral Statistics Field | Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

Dinas Komunikasi dan Informatika Kabupaten Majalengka

Collecting data, processing, and presenting sectoral statistical data in Majalengka Regency

#### ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

#### Head of Data Analyst Division | Mar 2020 - Dec Forum Kajian Statistika, Statistics, Padjadjaran University

Chief Executive of the Statistics Data Science Webinar Series, Leading statistical training to members and or general Fokasi.